Office of the Boards of Advisors Records UA200
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Veterinary Board of Overseers, 1988 -- 2020; UA200.012; 2.4 Linear Feet; 21 Digital Object(s) Of the 21 digital objects in this series, 2 represent zip files comprising 5 files and .16 MBs of data.
  - Report from the Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2009-05-12; UA200.012.016.00013; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-05-07; UA200.012.016.00014; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-11-02; UA200.012.016.00015; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine Board of Overseers Meeting, 2010-10-21; UA200.012.016.00016; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Veterinary, 2005 -- 2015; UA200.012.020 (Box 20)
  - Veterinary meeting minutes, 2016 -- 2018; UA200.012.00001; 4 Digital Object(s); .12 Megabytes
  - Cummings School Board of Advisors Minutes, 2018-11-16, UA200.012.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Cummings Board of Advisors Meeting Minutes, 2019-05-10; UA200.012.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 35 Kilobytes
  - Report from the Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine at Tufts University Board of Advisors Meeting, 2019 November 08; UA200.000740; 38.47 Megabytes
  - Report from Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine at Tufts University Board of Advisors Meeting, 2020 May 01; UA200.000748; 35.1 Kilobytes
- Meeting Minutes, 1897 -- 2008; 1988 -- 2006; UA200.013; 1.2 Linear Feet; 4 Digital Object(s)
  This series includes meeting minutes from the multiple Boards of Overseers. Paper files were received together in binders. Also included are copies of minutes from the original Board of Overseers which existed from 1899-1907.
  - Past Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, 1897 -- 1931; UA200.013.005.00014 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Past Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes 1897-1931 [2 of 3], UA200.013.005.00015 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Past Board of Overseers Meeting, 1897 -- 1931; UA200.013.005.00016 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Council of the Board of Overseers May 1995 to Present, 1995 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00017 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Arts and Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes Nov. 1994- May 2004 [Binder 1 of 11], 1994 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00018 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Athletic Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes Nov. 1988- April 2004 [Binder 2 of 11], 1998 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00019 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Dental Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, June 1988- April 2004 [Binder, 3 of 11], 1988 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00020 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, June1989- May 2004 [Binder 4 of 11], 1989 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00021 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Fletcher School Board of Overseers, Meeting Minutes, Oct 1993- April 2004 [Binders 5 of 11], 1993 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00022 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - International Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Sept 1988- June 2004 [Binder 6 of 11], 1998 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00023 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - University Library Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, March 1988- April 2000 [Binder 7 of 11], 1988 -- 2000; UA200.013.005.00024 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Medical/ Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Feb 1988- April 2004 [Binder 8 of 11], 1988 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00025 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Nutrition School Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, May 1994 - May 2004 [Binder 9 of 11], 1994 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00026 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - UCCPS Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Oct 1988- May 2004 [Binder 10 of 11], 1988 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00027 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Oct 1988- May 2004 [Binder 11 of 11], 1988 -- 2004; UA200.013.005.00028 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Arts and Sciences Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Fall 2004 to Present [Fall 2005] [Binder 1 of 10], 2004 -- 2005; UA200.013.005.00029 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Athletics Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Fall 2004 to Present [Spring 2005] [Binder, 2 of 10], 2004 -- 2005; UA200.013.005.00030 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Dental Board of Overseers, Meeting Minutes, Fall 2004 to Present [Fall 2005] [Binder 3 of 10], 2004 -- 2005; UA200.013.005.00031 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Engineering Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Fall 2004 to Present [Spring 2006][Binder, 4 of 10], 2004 -- 2006; UA200.013.005.00032 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Fletcher School Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes Fall 2004 to Present [Fall 2005] [Binder 5 of 10], 2004 -- 2005; UA200.013.005.00033 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Medical/ Sackler Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Fall 2004 to Present [Spring 2005] [Binder 6 of 10], 2004 -- 2005; UA200.013.005.00034 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Nutrition Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Fall 2004 to Present [Fall 2005] [Binder 7 of 10], 2004 -- 2005; UA200.013.005.00035 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Tisch College Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Fall 2004 to Present [Spring 2006] [Binder 8 of 10], 2004 -- 2006; UA200.013.005.00036 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Veterinary Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Fall 2004 to Present [Fall 2005] [Binder 9 of 10], UA200.013.005.00037 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - International Board of Overseers Meeting Minutes, Fall 2004 to Present [Summer 2005] [Binder 10 of 10], 2004 -- 2005; UA200.013.005.00038 (Box UA200 Shared 1)
  - Enclosure C - Boards of Overseers Reports, 2004; UA200.013.011.00001; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Includes: Fletcher, October 18, 2004; Nutrition, October 27, 2004; Arts and Sciences, November 4, 2004; University College of Citizenship and Public Service, November 9, 2004
  - Enclosure E - Boards of Overseers Reports, 2004; UA200.013.011.00002; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Includes: Medical/Sackler - April 28, 2004 and October 20, 2004; Nutrition - May 4-5, 2004; Veterinary - May 24, 2004 and October 26, 2004; International - June 10-11, 2004 and November 12-13, 2004; Athletics - October 7, 2004; Engineering - October 14, 2004; Dental - November 16, 2004
  - Enclosure F - Boards of Overseers Reports, 2004-09-14; UA200.013.011.00003; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Includes: Council of Boards of Overseers, February 9, 2004; Athletics, April 13, 2004; Fletcher, February 9, 2004 and April 27, 2004; Dental, April 30, 2004; Arts and Sciences, May 6, 2004; Engineering, May 11, 2004; UCCPS, May 13, 2004
  - Letter on research to all Board Members, 2008-02-08; UA200.013.011.00004; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Letter on research to all Board Members
- Biographical Files, 1923 -- 2016; 1982 -- 2007; UA200.014; 6.0 Linear Feet
  This series consists of biographical files on Boards of Overseers members compiled by the Office of the Boards of Overseers for internal reference.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Bendetson, Norris, 1988 -- 1995; UA200.014.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Berenberg, Roslyn, 1996 -- 2001; UA200.014.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Berger, Louis, 1989 -- 1996; UA200.014.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Bernstein, Irene, 1989 -- 1995; UA200.014.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Brooks, Harvey, 1988 -- 2004; UA200.014.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Burn, Barbara, 2000 -- 2002; UA200.014.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Calebresi, Paul, 1997 -- 2003; UA200.014.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Ciardi Alexandra, 1997 -- 2005; UA200.014.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Cook, Jane B., 1982 -- 2002; UA200.014.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Coolidge, Thomas Jefferson UCCPS Overseer, 1998 -- 2005; UA200.014.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Cleveland, Richard A54 (International), 2000 -- 2002; UA200.014.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Dowling, John L. - A&S Overseer Trustee also, 1999 -- 2004; UA200.014.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Flagg, John F. (Vet), 1993 -- 2004; UA200.014.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Florence, Leonard, 1998 -- 2006; UA200.014.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Fong, Senator Hiram Leong Int'l., 1993 -- 2004; UA200.014.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Galletti, Pierre, 1989 -- 1997; UA200.014.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Herndon, Noah, 1995 -- 1999; UA200.014.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Ira Katz, 1994 -- 2000; UA200.014.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Kohnstamm, Paul, 1990 -- 2001; UA200.014.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Leach, Kenneth, 1989 -- 1996; UA200.014.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Lewis, Stanley A., 1988 -- 1998; UA200.014.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Mason, Austin B., 1988 -- 2002; UA200.014.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Nickerson, Pauline M., 1923 -- 2001; UA200.014.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Mac Janet, Charlotte, 1988 -- 1999; UA200.014.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - McDermott, Sheila A., 1989 -- 2007; UA200.014.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - McGrath Jr., David J., 1989 -- 1995; UA200.014.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Miller, Lloyd, 1995 -- 2007; UA200.014.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Moseley, James B., 1988 -- 1998; UA200.014.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Moynihan, Daniel, 2000 -- 2003; UA200.014.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - O'Neill, John T. (International Ovr) E50, 1999 -- 2004; UA200.014.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - O'Neill, John T. Chair, 1988 -- 2004; UA200.014.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - O'Neill, John T., 1988 -- 1998; UA200.014.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Rudzik, Allan, 1995 -- 1997; UA200.014.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Susan Saltonstall, 1990 -- 1994; UA200.014.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - Shapiro, Samuel, 1995 -- 2001; UA200.014.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - Silverman, Norman, 1991 -- 2006; UA200.014.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - Simensen, A. Martin, 1990 -- 1995; UA200.014.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - Stein, Myron, 1988 -- 2004; UA200.014.006.00038 (Box 6)
  - Tarr, David, 1990 -- 2000; UA200.014.006.00039 (Box 6)
  - Tomasso, William J., 1988 -- 1992; UA200.014.006.00040 (Box 6)
  - Vance, Cyrus, 1998 -- 2002; UA200.014.006.00041 (Box 6)
  - Waring, Lloyd, 1979 -- 1988; UA200.014.006.00042 (Box 6)
  - Wright, H. Dudley, 1988 -- 1992; UA200.014.006.00043 (Box 6)
  - Wriston, Walter, 1995; UA200.014.006.00044 (Box 6)
  - Zimman, Harold O., 1988 -- 1994; UA200.014.006.00045 (Box 6)
  - Deceased advisors; Released/retired advisors, A-B, 1999 -- 2016; UA200.014.026 (Box 26)
  - Released/retired advisors, C-K, 1999 -- 2016; UA200.014.027 (Box 27)
  - Released/retired advisors, L-S, 1999 -- 2016; UA200.014.028 (Box 28)
  - Released/retired advisors, S-Z, 1999 -- 2016; UA200.014.029 (Box 29)
- Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Meeting Minutes and Materials, 2003 -- 2020; UA200.015; 1.2 Linear Feet; 20 Digital Object(s) Of the 20 digital objects in this series, two represent zip files comprising 5 files and .16 MBs of data.
  This series includes meeting minutes and meeting materials from the Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board of Overseers. This College was formerly known as University College.
  - Report from the University College Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-05-12; UA200.015.017.00001; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the University College Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the University College Board of Overseers Meeting, 2005-11-14; UA200.015.017.00002; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Tisch College Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-05-12; UA200.015.017.00003; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the Tisch Board of Overseers Meeting
  - Report from the Tisch College Board of Overseers Meeting, 2006-11-09; UA200.015.017.00004; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting, 2007-04-27; UA200.015.017.00005; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting April 27, 2007
  - Tisch Conference Call, 2009-03-01; UA200.015.017.00006; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Multiple documents regarding a Conference call concerning the operations of the Tisch College.
  - Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting, 2007-10-25; UA200.015.017.00007; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting
  - Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting, 2008-11-12; UA200.015.017.00008; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting, 2009-04-22; UA200.015.017.00009; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting, 2009-10-14; UA200.015.017.00010; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting, 2010-04-21; UA200.015.017.00011; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting, 2010-11-10; UA200.015.017.00012; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Report from the Joint Meeting of the Boards: School of Arts and Sciences and Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service, 2011-10-20; UA200.015.017.00013; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Report from the Joint Meeting of the Boards: School of Arts and Sciences and Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service
  - Appendix to the Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting, 2011-10-20; UA200.015.017.00014; Office of the Boards of Overseers
    Appendix to the Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting
  - Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service Board Meeting, 2011-10-20; UA200.015.017.00015; Office of the Boards of Overseers
  - Tisch College, 2003 -- 2015; UA200.015.025 (Box 25)
    Meeting agendas, minutes, and materials, Fall 2003-Spring 2015.
  - Tisch College meeting minutes, 2016 -- 2018; UA200.015.00001; 4 Digital Object(s); .12 Megabytes
  - Tisch College Board of Advisors Minutes, 2018-11-28, UA200.015.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tisch College Board of Advisors Meeting Minutes, 2019-04-12; UA200.015.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 33 Kilobytes
  - Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Civic Life Board of Advisors Meeting, 2019 October 25; UA200.000745; 40.91 Megabytes
  - Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Civic Life Board of Advisors Meeting, 2020 April 17; UA200.000754; 22.2 Kilobytes
- Additional accessions, UA200.016; 46 Digital Object(s)
  - Multiple Board minutes, 2010 -- 2012; UA200-001
    75 years from the date of creation.
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for -Arts & Sciences, Athletics, Engineering, Medical, 2012; UA200-002
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for -Arts & Sciences, 2012; UA200-003
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Cummings Vet, 2012; UA200-004
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Sackler, 2012; UA200-005
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Dental and Athletics, 2012; UA200-006
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Fletcher, 2012; UA200-007
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Friedman, 2012; UA200-008
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Engineering, 2012; UA200-009
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Council and Tisch, 2012; UA200-010
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Cummings, 2009; UA200-011
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for A&S, 2009; UA200-012
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for A&S, 2010; UA200-013
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Tisch College, 2012-11-13; UA200-014
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Fletcher School, 2012-10-05; UA200-015
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Arts and Sciences, 2013-02-21; UA200-016
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Cummings School, 2012-10-23; UA200-017
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Friedman School, 2012-10-10; UA200-018
  - Boards of Advisor Minutes for Dental, 2013-01-30; UA200-019
  - Boards of Advisor Council Minutes, 2013-02-06; UA200-020
  - International Boards of Advisor Minutes, 2012-12-07; UA200-021
  - Athletics Boards of Advisor Minutes, 2013-04-04; UA200-022
  - Arts and Sciences Boards of Advisor Minutes, 2013-04-11; UA200-023
  - Arts and Sciences Boards of Advisor Minutes, 2013-04-11; UA200-024
    Possible duplicate or update of UA200-023.
  - Athletic Board of Advisor Minutes, 2013-04-04; UA200-025
  - Cumming School of Veterinary Board of Advisor Minutes, 2013-05-09; UA200-026
  - Dental Board of Advisor Minutes, 2013-05-03; UA200-027
  - Engineering Board of Advisor Minutes, 2013-04-23; UA200-028
  - Friedman School Board of Advisor Minutes, 2013-05-13; UA200-029
  - Medical School Board of Advisor Minutes, 2013-04-25; UA200-030
  - Tisch College Board of Advisor Minutes, 2013-04-30; UA200-031
  - International Board of Advisor Minutes, 2013-06; UA200-032
  - Multiple Board meeting minutes, 2014 -- 2015; UA200-043
  - Council of the Board of Advisors minutes, 2015-02-05; UA200-044
  - Dental Board of Advisors minutes, 2015-04-25; UA200-045
  - Engineering Board of Advisors minutes, 2015-04-09; UA200-046
  - Fletcher School Board of Advisors minutes, 2015-05-15; UA200-047
  - International Board of Advisors minutes, 2015-06-06; UA200-048
  - Tisch College Board of Advisors minutes, 2015-04-10; UA200-049
  - Multiple Board minutes, 2013 -- 2014; UA200-050
  - Multiple Board minutes, 2015-04 -- 2015-10; UA200-051
    Boards of Advisors minutes for Dental, Cummings, Athletics, and Friedman, April 2015 - October 2015
  - Medical School and Tisch College Boards of Advisors minutes, 2015-10; UA200-052
    Boards of Advisors minutes for the Medical School and Tisch College, October 2015
  - Multiple Board agendas, 2011 -- 2015; UA200-053
  - Minutes and agendas, 1994 -- 2014; UA200-054
  - UCCPS_Waitlisted_Fryer_Coin_Legacy, 2005; UA200.056; 19 Digital Object(s)
  - Waitlisted_From_the_Fryer_to_the_Freeway_Flip_the_Coin_Melanies_Legacy, 2005; UA200.015.025.003; 442.5 Megabytes; 19
- Report from the Tufts University Athletics Board of Advisors meeting, 2020 October 16; UA200.000755; 33.77 Kilobytes
- Report from the School of Arts and Sciences Board of Advisors meeting, 2020 October 02; UA200.000756; 40.23 Kilobytes
- Report from the School of Dental Medicine Board of Advisors meeting, 2020 November 13; UA200.000757; 28.24 Kilobytes
- Report from the School of Engineering Board of Advisors meeting, 2020 October 23; UA200.000758; 31.5 Kilobytes
- Report from The Fletcher School Board of Advisors meeting, 2020 October 16; UA200.000759; 46.35 Kilobytes
- Report from the Tufts University International Board of Advisors meeting, 2020 October 21; UA200.000760; 30.02 Kilobytes
- Report from the meeting of the Board of Advisors to the School of Medicine, 2020 October 06; UA200.000761; 35.42 Kilobytes
- Report from the Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy Board of Advisors meeting, 2020 March 31; UA200.000762; 31.24 Kilobytes
- Report from the Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy Board of Advisors meeting, 2020 October 26; UA200.000763; 33.43 Kilobytes
- Report from Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine at Tufts University Board of Advisors meeting, 2020 November 06; UA200.000764; 40.04 Kilobytes
- Report from the Jonathan M. Tisch College of Civic Life Board of Advisors meeting, 2020 November 06; UA200.000765; 33.02 Kilobytes